Previously on Reacher...
Whoever did this weren't amateurs.
ME needs to take a look at the knife
the guy that took a run at me used,
- see if it matches these wounds.
- Okay.
Whatever is on that drive
is the property of the United States Army,
and I just want to see it get returned
to the Pentagon where it belongs.
The jump drive.
Anna had it when she left for Philly.
I think I know where she put it.
She mailed the drive,
and maybe her phone,
before getting on the subway.
A woman kills herself
on the same train as the chief of staff
of a potential presidential candidate.
CIA starts kidnapping people over it.
Let's do it the easy way
- this time, Reacher.
- No.
- [intense music playing]
- [grunting]
It appears Ben's throat was cut
with a curved knife.
Resembles a claw.
It's called a karambit,
used by practitioners
of certain martial arts in Indonesia.
[suspenseful music playing]
Philly PD! Hands up! Hands up!
[sirens wailing in distance]
[officer] Hands behind your head.
- [tense music playing]
- [officer over radio] Alpha Team.
Perimeter secure.
I didn't do this.
Shut the fuck up. On your knees.
Bravo Two, holding position.
[intense music playing]
[gunshot]
- [officer 2] Shots fired.
- [siren wailing]
♪ ♪
[grunting softly]
- [grunting]
- [cloth rips, stops]
[SWAT leader muffled] We need backup
at Liberty Gardens Hotel.
Six bodies, suspect on the run.
Caucasian male, six-four, uh, six-five,
250 pounds,
likely armed.
- [suspenseful music playing]
- [trash chute opens]
[officer over radio] We should move on.
Echo only.
Second floor clear.
[radio transmission echoing]
♪ ♪
[grunts]
[panting]
Oof.
- [phone beeps]
- [horns honking]
[line rings]
[phone ringing]
It's Reacher.
Been trying to call you
for the last 20 minutes.
Thought you might be dead.
Not me, but a lot of other people.
Four Reds and Lila's bodyguards,
all dead in her hotel room.
Cops showed while I was there.
- Shit.
- They think I did it.
Barely got away.
We need to find out
who took Lila and Amisha.
Reacher, I don't think anyone took them.
The bodies you saw,
their throats were slashed?
Thick cuts, like we saw
on the OnlyFans girl?
Yeah. Reds were cut up like that.
How'd you know?
[Tamara] Med examiner said
both Mary Ellen Daniels and Ben
were killed with a curved blade
with a wide tip called a karambit.
A weapon specifically from Indonesia.
Where's your girl from, Reacher?
[intense music playing]
I got it wrong.
[Russell] Lila and Amisha
came back to the room,
found their guards dead
and the Reds waiting for them.
They sliced 'em and ran.
They weren't kidnapped.
[Tamara] They gamed us the whole time.
She and Amisha hired Mary Ellen
to seduce your nephew,
then killed her and abducted Ben.
Anna never would've mailed
that thumb drive to Lila.
She was trying to keep it away from her.
She mailed it to someone else.
Someone who'd do anything to help her,
someone she trusted more than anybody.
Her brother.
That drive could've been sitting
in Jacob's mailbox
since at least this morning.
- You need to go get it. Now.
- [sirens wailing]
- [Tamara] And what are you gonna do?
- Run.
[intense music playing]
Freeze!
- [brakes screech]
- [horn blares]
[grunts]
Don't fucking move!
[thunder rumbling]
[♪ The Plimsouls sing
"Million Miles Away"]
You know, I can drive.
- Maybe you should--
- We're almost there.
♪ Friday night, I'd just got back...
Gives me something to focus on.
♪ was dreaming about the past...
But thanks for offering.
[Russell] Oh, man.
- What?
- Well, I asked some trusted sources
from the dark web if they could dig up
anything on Amisha and Lila.
Amisha's a ghost, but a financial hacker
I know just found something on Lila.
Scrooge McFuck?
That's just his handle. All right?
He's totally trustworthy,
and he discovered that,
up until a few weeks ago,
Lila Hoth had zero economic fingerprint.
She had no mortgages, bank accounts,
student loans, not even a credit score.
That's because the names Lila Hoth
and Amisha Hoth are bullshit.
Exactly. But then, out of nowhere,
a Platinum Amex card under Lila's name
with a six-figure limit
shows up in the system.
A few weeks ago, she uses it
to buy first-class plane tickets
from Indonesia to the U.S. for Lila Hoth,
Amisha Hoth, and their two bodyguards.
Then, more recently, she bought
a fifth ticket for a flight from Djibouti
that landed here this morning.
- Who's from Djibouti?
- [Russell] I don't know.
McFuck's running a trace
on that ticket now,
but whatever name he comes up with,
it's gonna be a fake, bogus passport,
but... [scoffs]
...the Hoths obviously brought this guy
into the U.S. to do something.
Well, whatever it is, it's not good.
♪ There was no one around,
to the place that ♪
[birds singing]
We'll be right back.
Keep doing your thing.
Roger that.
[tense, suspenseful music playing]
This is Anna's handwriting.
There you are, you little fucker.
[soft chuckle]
Her phone.
011806.
- Ben's birthday.
- She gave you her password.
What's this?
Tomas Waberi.
What are you up to?
[Jacob] It's dead.
[sighs] And my charger isn't compatible.
We'll buy you a new one,
but for right now,
let's get that drive into Plum's laptop.
[engine revs]
Tamara.
That car.
[intense music playing]
[Tamara] Go!
Go. Go. Go, go, go, go!
[line ringing]
[dispatch over phone] 911.
What's your emergency?
This is Detective Tamara Green
with the Philadelphia PD.
I'm with a Mayfield police officer
and a civilian
in an unmarked blue Ford Taurus
headed north on...
- Where the fuck are we?
- Parsons Avenue.
Parsons Ave. Black SUV
with two armed adult females
in active pursuit of our vehicle.
We need backup now!
Help!
[dispatch] Copy, Detective.
We're sending units your way.
Please stay on the line.
[grunts]
[speaking Indonesian]
Don't let them get away.
Won't happen.
Go faster!
Hold on. I'm gonna try something.
[engine revving]
Whoa, whoa, you're going too fast.
We're gonna wind up in the river.
Rite of passage in high school
to make this turn at full speed.
We all did it. Lila didn't.
Holy shit.
I thought you made this turn
in high school?
I did, and I slammed my dad's Maxima
right into the bridge.
[dramatic music playing]
They crashed.
[brakes screeching]
We still got trouble.
[Lila screams, pants]
[suspenseful music playing]
We've got the flash drive,
and their ride is shot.
Drive away before we all end up dead.
If we run, they'll run, too.
I'm keeping them on the bridge
until backup gets here.
They got automatic weapons.
If you don't like
what I'm about to do...
get out.
Be smart.
You haven't lost what I've lost.
I only got seven rounds left.
So let's make 'em count.
[intense music playing]
[gunfire]
Ah!
[both grunt]
I'm sorry.
[siren wailing in distance]
We have to go!
No, they have the drive!
We can't sell anything if we're dead!
Lila!
Now!
Fuck! [screams]
[officer] Get off the railing
and onto the ground.
- No. No! No!
- What?
No!
- [officer] Show me your hands!
- Philly PD!
- They got away!
From this height,
there's a good chance they're dead.
[officer] Hands!
[gun cocks]
Toss the badge.
[low, dramatic music playing]
[door closes in distance]
[door opens]
[door closes]
[footsteps approaching]
You know, this isn't the first time
Green's been caught up in trouble.
And the first time
wasn't her fault, either.
Screwed by some political burn job.
Now, the kid's getting the high hard one
again, thanks to you.
Oh, it's my fault?
She's good police. I always figured,
soon enough, she'd find her old gear
and climb out of the hole she got kicked
into, but then, you come along,
drag her into this bullshit.
And now, you're worried she'll be working
with some washed-up,
bullshit, half-in-the-bag cop forever.
That I am.
Speaking of bullshit, want to explain why
Giant Boxcar Willie's got the personal
cell number of a presidential candidate?
And don't tell me it's fake.
I called and hung up,
guy who answered sounded
just like the one I've seen on TV.
What the hell
do you have Tamara tied up in?
If I tell you, will you help me?
Fuck no.
Then shove that card up your ass.
[door opens]
[sighs]
[door closes]
[entry bell jingles]
Yeah, got the biggest one they had.
I'll pick up ice cream on the way home.
I know, but no tonsils
equals a lot of spoiling.
[chuckles] Okay.
See you soon.
- Love you, too.
- [woman] Excuse me, sir?
[choking]
[tense music playing]
- All right. That should do it.
- [clears throat]
Just treat it with antibiotic ointment
twice a day for three days,
- should be good.
- All right.
Thanks, Terry.
[Russell] Look, the screen is busted.
There's no way we're gonna be able to read
the drive on this thing.
District hardware's a no-go.
The less they o-or anyone else knows
about this drive, the better.
- So, this stays between us and Reacher.
- Okay.
I should check in with him.
[knock on door]
- Yeah?
- [door opens]
Jakey?
We're ok, Unc.
I was in Hackensack when I got the call
about the bridge.
First Anna, now this?
Guys, this is, uh,
Lieutenant Monty DeRosa.
He keeps the Mayfield station running.
Uncle Monty, this is Detective
Tamara Green and Russell Plum.
- They're friends of mine.
- [Russell] So...
policing, what, it's a family business?
[chuckles]
I was his dad's partner for years.
He's been calling me uncle
since he was a kid. [chuckles]
With everything that's happening, I don't
see how you're even still standing.
I mean, I can barely function.
How-How's Ben holding up?
[somber music playing]
Ben... [exhales]
Ben was murdered, Unc.
Oh, God.
What the hell's going on here, son?
We don't know yet,
but the two women
who jumped off the bridge,
they're behind all of it.
Yeah, I know it's a lot.
Yeah, it-it's more than you realize.
Those women are not done killing.
[suspenseful music playing]
Meaning?
Merle Harkavey.
He was found dead.
Jugular slashed over on Pleasant Avenue,
and a witness said they saw
two soaking wet women
jump in his car and drive off.
They're alive.
[siren wailing in distance]
You fish your gun out?
Nah.
Got an oldie but a goodie right here.
You know, you should've
gone with me in Baltimore.
- Now, the rules have changed.
- Let me guess.
Real cops are gonna
find me hanging dead in here
'cause I couldn't take the guilt
from all those things I didn't do.
That's about right.
So, cry to your God.
Scream for help.
Nobody's gonna hear you
through the cinderblock.
Oh.
There was something else
that I was supposed to tell you.
You lose, Reacher.
[gun cocks]
[intense music playing]
[grunts, shouts]
[screaming]
[whimpering]
- You son of a bitch.
- You'll be fine.
I knew a kid in Maine who was missing one.
He turned out okay.
No.
No, no, no, no, no. [grunts]
[dramatic music playing]
[Reacher exhales]
We can't bring the Feds in.
- Just trust me on this, please.
- [Monty] This is not about trust.
This is about reality.
This case is too goddamn big
for the Mayfield police department.
The Feds will take over.
They will box me out.
They have the resources to deal
with this kind of thing.
It is my family that they murdered!
I'm taking these animals in,
not the fucking Feds.
[Monty] These are stone-cold killers.
Have you seen what they've been doing?
They're dropping bodies right and left.
They're shooting at police officers.
This is out of our league.
This is a federal matter.
You call the FBI,
you tell 'em what you know,
and you let them do their job.
Okay, Unc.
We have reason to believe the Feds
might be trying to cover this up, okay?
CIA is part of it, too. I...
I didn't want to tell you.
I don't want you involved.
Why would the government do that?
We're not sure.
Which branch of the Feds is it?
- We have no idea.
- [Monty] You don't know.
[sighs] Jake.
You are too smart to hang your hat
on a bunch of question marks.
You don't know who. You don't know why.
You just think that
the Feds might be involved?
That's all you got?
[distant chatter]
Okay.
All right. I'll call them. I'll...
- Good boy.
- I'll fill 'em in on everything.
- [Monty] Good.
- Come on, man. You--
No, no, no, no, no.
We are a demoted detective,
a small-town cop, and a goddamn blogger.
- We're in over our heads.
- [Monty] That's right.
That's a good boy. You call 'em.
[sighs] Now, I'm hungry.
I'm gonna order some food.
You guys look like you could use it.
[door opens]
I'm not calling the fucking FBI.
[Monty] All right, once more for safety.
Fifteen cheese, 15 no onions,
three bags of fries, six-pack of Cokes.
- Charge it to the PD account.
- [cashier] Copy that.
Okay, thanks.
- [cashier] Sure thing.
- [call ends]
Hey, the FBI will be here in an hour,
and we're just gonna step outside
for some air.
- Hell of a day.
- [Monty] Well, take your time.
Just ordered White Manna.
Should be here in a bit.
Thanks.
I appreciate it.
[line ringing]
Still no answer.
Think someone maybe got him?
I don't know.
[phone rings]
[phone beeps]
- Hello?
- [Reacher over phone] It's me.
[Tamara] What the hell happened to you?
Cops arrested me, but I got out.
[Tamara] What do you mean "got out"?
Means I'm stacking up charges.
You get the drive?
And Anna's phone, but it's dead,
and my laptop was shot.
- Shot?
- [Tamara] Lila and Amisha wound up
at Jacob's. We got away,
but they know we have the drive.
Where are you now?
Heading to Philly in Jacob's cruiser.
Stolen cruiser.
[Reacher] Lila and Amisha?
[Russell] Looking for us.
They're looking for the drive.
[Tamara] In a car they jacked in Mayfield.
Sliced a man's throat to get it.
- Is he alive?
- [Jacob] Merle bled out on the street.
He was a good man.
Had three daughters.
There's a BOLO, but Lila'll swap out
cars if she hasn't already.
I'm sorry, but where are we going?
If Lila and Amisha are after us,
and the Philly cops are after Reacher...
And the CIA.
They're gonna be pissed
after what I just did.
[Tamara] Stay in the city and lie low.
We'll meet at the corner of G Street
and East Allegheny,
one block east of K and A.
No police stations in the area, and
there's an electronics store on the corner
so we can grab a charger
and a new laptop.
- How far out are you?
- [Tamara] We'll be there in
70 minutes.
Make it 90.
The sliders should be getting
to the station soon.
Monty'll come looking for us,
see that we took off and put out an alert.
We gotta ditch this cruiser.
- [♪ Mykal sings "No Reason"]
- ♪ having a reason ♪
♪ She say that she love me,
but only want money ♪
♪ I switch out my bread like the season ♪
♪ I always stunt on the 'gram,
I just buy what I want ♪
♪ You gonna know when you see me,
I always...
You got to be shittin' me.
♪ I live like a boss, and I mean it,
back on my bully...
Stay by the car. What up, Cyrus?
How's the cat?
The cat? Tore up my sister's BarcaLounger.
Now she says I got to get her a new one.
So, if y'all came to give me a puppy,
get gone.
No pets this time. Need a ride.
- You got a ride.
- That's staying here.
You ain't leaving no fucking
cop car at my spot.
Park it out back and throw a tarp over it.
♪ at you, at you,
Skittles got me feeling sick...
Or I could just seize everything in here
that doesn't have a bill of sale,
down to the last hubcap.
♪ As long as the 80 is loaded and my
fingers rolling, then we gonna be rich ♪
♪ My life is different...
[sighs]
Shit, man. Why you always trying
to fuck with my pocket?
♪ but only want money,
I switch out my bread like the season ♪
[vehicle approaching]
Nice ride.
Got it from an old friend.
So, you want to tell us how you got out
of Philly PD custody?
[Muzak playing]
- The entire ear?
- [elevator bell dings]
Not this one.
[elevator bell dings]
Not this one, either.
[elevator doors slide closed]
[elevator bell dings]
This'll work.
[speaking Spanish]
How'd you like to make some extra cash?
Do you speak English?
A little...
You're cleaning this room
hours after final checkout,
so you're not rushing to get it ready
for the next occupant.
No harm in letting us use it
for a few hours.
Everybody wins.
You're braver than I am.
[computer beeps]
All right, let's take a look.
Sampson, Cahill.
That must be General Putra.
- What the fuck is this?
- [phone chimes]
It's charged.
[Reacher] I said I'd know what to do with
the drive once I saw what was on it, but
I don't even know what I'm looking at.
We have mercenaries, Feds, the CIA, and
Indonesian killers all after this thing,
and we still don't know why.
There are no other files on here.
- None of this makes any sense.
- Why would anyone kill over this?
I found Anna's last text chain.
It was with a blocked number.
That's got to be Lila.
She sent Anna an address in Philly
the night she died.
Where they were supposed to meet.
That's where we're headed to next.
190 East... 190 East...
First floor is an abandoned restaurant.
Looks like it's under
some kind of renovation.
Lila sent a video...
right before the address.
- No.
- Jacob...
- [Ben over video] Stop.
- [Mary screaming over video]
- [Ben] Please stop!
- [Lila] Tell your mother.
Mom, they're cutting her up.
They say I'm next
if you don't do what they say.
Stop. Please.
There's another one.
Don't see what you can't unsee.
[tense music playing]
Hey. He shouldn't be out there alone.
He's not gonna jump.
I just think someone should be with him.
Keep checking the phone,
see if you can find anything useful.
[bird singing]
[traffic passing below]
I'm gonna hurt them...
...like they hurt my family.
I will take their knives
and dig them deep into their guts.
Slaughter them
like the animals they are.
I don't know you very well,
but I know that's not who you are.
That's not the person
Anna and Ben loved.
That person's as dead as they are.
I won't let you spin out.
[news anchor over TV] A breaking story
now. Police are urging
citizens of Philadelphia
and the Delaware Valley area
to be on the lookout for this man,
who assaulted
a police officer and escaped custody
just hours ago.
The fugitive, Jack Reacher,
was apprehended earlier today
in relation to multiple homicides.
He's described as a white male,
six-foot-five, and 250 pounds.
At over six-foot-three inches
and 250 pounds...
- [phone chiming and buzzing]
- ...Jack Reacher is considered to be
extremely dangerous.
- [TV turns off]
- [phone continues chiming and buzzing]
- Here we go.
- [phone beeps]
You are all over the fucking news,
so this better be good.
Why are people dying over a photo of you,
Cahill, and Putra from over 25 years ago?
So, you found the drive.
Is that what was on it?
A photo?
[Reacher] And nothing else.
As far as I can tell,
it's nothing worth killing over.
Well, it's got to be blackmail, then.
Evidence of collaboration with Putra
would be a blow to my campaign.
Bullshit. I already told you, bin Laden
and Hussein were our allies once.
Plenty of politicians cozied up to them
without losing their careers over it.
And no offense,
that's a hell of a lot of carnage
just to derail a congressman
from North Carolina.
Then I don't know what's special
about that photograph.
Maybe the other guy in the photo does.
- Show him.
- Yeah, sure.
[laptop whooshes]
[phone chimes]
Well, he's not Delta.
He was just a scientist
doing malaria research down there.
What's his name?
[John] No idea. I didn't have anything
to do with the scientists.
That was Cahill's assignment.
I spent all my time working
with Putra's men.
What he was doing in that room?
It was 25 years ago, I don't know.
That's your answer for everything.
You're in the perfect line of work,
you know that, Congressman?
[John] What, do you want me to lie to you?
Look, I am as confused
about all this as you are.
The one thing I do know is that
I'm looking at a news report
saying you killed a bunch of people
inside of a hotel,
and then broke out of jail
after assaulting a cop.
[Reacher] He wasn't a cop. He was CIA.
And if I'm so guilty,
why are you still talking to me?
- Good point.
- [phone beeps]
[news anchor over TV] The injured officer
was transported to a local hospital,
and though severely injured,
is believed to be in
non-life-threatening condition.
Authorities are asking for anyone...
Hey, guys? Sorry to interrupt,
but you need to see this.
...dial 911. Again--
The injured police officer was--
-...to a local hospital and though--
- [Russell] Oh, dear.
[reporter] He's possibly armed
-and extremely dangerous.
- Uh, it's every channel.
- Do not approach him.
- [siren wailing]
[tense, dramatic music playing]
We got six RPCs headed our way.
- They should've sent more.
- Next move?
Every cop in Philly thinks
I assaulted one of their own.
They'll be out for blood.
If we're gonna make it to the restaurant
in Anna's texts,
we need to split into two groups.
Jacob, take Plum to the library.
Use the public internet to find
the scientist in that photo.
No way. I'm going to that restaurant.
It's where my sister was headed
when she died.
Reacher's right. Plum's a civilian
who needs protection, and you're a cop.
You two need to get out of here.
Take the back stairwell.
Okay.
And what about you?
Easy.
I'm gonna get arrested again.
[elevator bell dings]
Don't move. Show me your hands.
Philly PD. Take it easy.
I got him. Move your big fucking ass.
[indistinct police radio chatter]
Suspect's in custody.
[officer] Can you please give me
a description of the people you saw?
Uh...
Wait! Stop them!
- They're together!
- Whoa, slow down, lady. No-no hablo.
That, uh, man is with the woman.
Oh, yes, she's arresting him.
We have everything under control.
No, no, no. Hold on.
You said those two are together?
Yes, then went into a hotel room!
Was he leading her?
Like a hostage?
No, the big guy and their two friends
went in first! She followed them in.
They all know each other!
[intense music playing]
Shit.
[siren wailing]
[officer over speakers] Philly PD.
Pull your car over now.
That didn't take long.
[brakes screeching]
Shit.
Get out.
In there.
[over radio] Do not rush in alone.
Wait for backup.
Copy. En route.
♪ ♪
- Freeze!
- [gunshots]
[siren wailing]
The hotel.
Philadelphia PD.
Active shooter. One block east.
Everyone stay inside.
Away from the windows.
Lock the doors, now.
[panicked chatter]
And whatever you do,
don't let anyone inside.
Back inside.
[officer] Philadelphia PD. Open up.
Open the goddamn door!
Come on. Let's go.
[Reacher] Shit.
[Tamara] What's the plan?
We're gonna rappel.
Fuck you.
Learned how to do it in the Army.
Two people, one harness.
The lines can hold our weight.
You just need to get on my back.
Wrap your legs around me.
I fall, I die.
Then don't fall.
[tense, suspenseful music playing]
Let's go.
[metal creaking]
- [yells]
- [grunts]
- Shit, shit, shit, shit.
- It's okay. It's okay.
- Hold on tight. Don't let go.
- All right.
[both scream]
Give me your hand.
- Ah!
[Tamara screams]
Ah...
[groans]
Oh, shit. Is that the glass?
[grunts] Spread your body weight out.
It's cracking.
Stay still. I'm coming to you.
Okay. I'm gonna take your hand,
I'm gonna pull you towards me.
- Okay.
- Hey.
Nice and slow. All right.
Got you.
Nice and easy.
Here we go.
[whimpers]
[grunts]
[officer] Freeze!
Show me your hands.
- Get on the ground!
- Tamara?
Huh?
Go limp.
- [both groan]
- [intense music playing]
Let's go!
[sirens wailing]
Bus.
Courtesy ride. Taking this guy with me.
[bus driver] All good.
[suspenseful music playing]
Not good.
That's the guy from the news. That guy.
That's the guy from the news!
Call the cops.
- [loud chatter]
- Call the cops!
Don't let him off.
[female passenger] Hey, hey, over there!
Hey. He went that way.
The guy who escaped today.
We wait ten minutes, then head
to the place on Anna's phone.
It's not that far from here.
Good.
I'm tired.
[percussive, dramatic music playing]
This is it.
Reacher.
[Reacher] Ben's blood.
[Tamara] Fully desiccated.
Probably been here a few days.
He was held here.
This is where he was killed.
That's where they tortured him.
They underestimated the strength
of a Division I athlete
full of fear-induced adrenaline.
He broke a restraint.
Unlatched the rest.
Ran for the door.
They barely got him in time.
Slit his throat before he could escape.
Let him bleed out
before they got rid of the body.
[Lila] He gave me no choice.
[tense, suspenseful music playing]
Give me the drive, Reacher.
Why would I do that?
It's her gun against your knife.
My knife.
And leverage.
I'm sorry.
I should've listened.
The drive.
Now.
- [♪ Cage the Elephant sings "Mess Around"]
- ♪ Ah ♪
- ♪ Oh, no ♪
♪ Oh, no ♪
- ♪ Ah ♪
- ♪ Oh, no ♪
♪ No, she don't mess around ♪
♪ Oh, St. Louie, California ♪
♪ Blue eyes, yeah, she's coming for you ♪
♪ Land of Mary, Charm City ♪
♪ Oh, Lord, wish she was my baby ♪
♪ You know she'll drive you crazy ♪
♪ Yeah, she's coming for you ♪
♪ No, she don't mess around ♪
- ♪ Ah ♪
- ♪ Oh, no ♪
♪ Ah ♪
♪ Oh, no ♪
♪ No, she don't mess around ♪
♪ The heat is rising
and only getting hotter ♪
♪ ready to blow ♪
♪ I think I'll pour myself
a glass of water ♪
♪ let it flow ♪
♪ She'll show you what she's made of ♪
♪ Yeah, she's coming for you ♪
♪ She's gonna try to break you ♪
♪ No, she don't mess around ♪
- ♪ Ah ♪
- ♪ Oh, no ♪
♪ Ah ♪
♪ Oh, no ♪
- ♪ Ah ♪
- ♪ Oh, no ♪
♪ No, she don't mess around ♪
♪ Oh, no ♪